<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to My Blogs on Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to My Blogs on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>fi-fi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 17:09:29 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>04 paid makaroni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 17:09:29 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;paid-makaroni&#34;&gt;Paid makaroni&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;People had gathered at my place—the same pre-Christmas party as in one of my earlier stories. In the midst of the festivities, I embarked on a noble (and completely unserious) quest: selling makaroni. Let’s just say I wouldn’t have made it as a salesman, as my only successful transaction was convincing Brandon to buy two packages at a price of 0.10€ per package (for reference, I believe they cost around 0.40€ at the grocery store at the time). The catch? I was the one who paid.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>03 Mailman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:09:29 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mail-man&#34;&gt;Mail man&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We gathered at Shea with a single mission: to present PowerPoints. The topic? Anything. Literally, anything. Yet, as fate would have it, Neo and I failed in our quest to create our own. For this, I was handed a random PowerPoint—a collection of slides bound by destiny alone. I had no knowledge of its contents. Only after some time did I realize it was about conspiracies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But before the actual gathering, I was on a crusade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>02 The Kitchen Roll Conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 20:31:29 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-kitchen-roll-conspiracy&#34;&gt;The Kitchen Roll Conspiracy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It all started with a pre-Christmas party—one that shouldn’t have happened at my apartment, at least not logically. My place was inconveniently far from my friends (a solid 10 km), and Tori, in particular, had made it a personal mission to complain about this fact at every possible opportunity. “I will never come again,” Tori had claimed every single time when in my place, and this is not a expection. And yet, on this one night, they arrived.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/prologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:41:21 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/prologue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Clock: Roughly 18:00. My next housewarming party.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As always, I was slightly behind on cleaning, so I met my guests at the door on my way to take out the trash. They stopped me—told me to close my eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I handed my keys to Tori and said, “It’s a blue one.” Confusion flickered across their faces, a hint of panic. Which blue? There were two blue keys. I left them to figure it out and continued with the trash.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preprologue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/preprologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:15:08 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/makaroni-blog/preprologue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a housewarming party after moving into an apartment inside a house that had been converted into multiple units. The guests arrived, bringing makaroni for me—lots of it. I gladly accepted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But then, there were Legos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Neo, ever the trickster, had cleverly disguised one of the makaroni packages. Instead of pasta, it contained Legos. And it wasn’t just Neo—Stella and Brandon had also contributed to the Lego chaos. I did the math—roughly 20 packages, each weighing 400 grams. That made 8 kilograms in total.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
